Bhrugu Tundeliya

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/bhrugu-tundeliya **Portfolio**: https://portfolio-bhrugu.vercel.app/

Github: https://github.com/Bhrugu14

StackOverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/7034453/bhrugu-tundeliya

15/16 Shyam Tenament Manjipura Road, Nadiad 387001

<u>(91) 8460304001</u>

bhrugu1409@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A passionate professional and a fast learner; with years of working experience in software design principles and agile development principles. worked independently as well as in a team for projects. Having expertise in mobile and web development

EXPERIENCE

Traffic Management Inc, USA— Frontend Developer

Mar 2023 - PRESENT

Technostacks Infotech Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad — *Software Developer*

July 2022 - Feb 2023

Codentic software, Anand — React Developer

October 2020 - June 2022

PROJECTS

Grocery Application— react native, typescript, git

Responsible for creating user and delivery partner's application from scratch, Implemented Family mode that handles group purchases, implemented Razorpay API

Catalog Application (Mobile and Website) — *Next.js, nodejs, React Native, git*

Build a Mobile responsive website for a product catalog with a modern eye-catching design. Working with the remote backend team for development. Integrated MirrAR Ar web plug-in for the try-on feature.

E-commerce sweets selling website — *Next.js, nodejs, git*

Responsible for bug fixes and design changes on the already developed website, rework on payment modules with different payment methods, and promo code integration.

BLE Connector — React Native, Typescript, git

Created a Mobile application that can detect specific service UUID and connect to it, send and receive messages via BLE.

Online Documents Storage — React js, Ionic, git

Responsible for client communication information gathering, design, and project development, managed role-based scenarios in folder options, and implemented reminder features with different ranges.

Rewards-Driven Application — *React Native, git*

Independently designed and developed the Front end of a mobile application, that detects users near the vendor's application with Socket, Vendor can send customer-related offers with that. implemented one-signal for notification

Online Menu, Promo QRCode generation, Club Application—

React Native, Next js, git

worked on an online menu project that gets dynamic URLs from QRcode, generates Lottery QRcode with vendor's admin panel, and also bug fixes on clubbing Application for Germany.

SKILLS

- React
- Next
- React Native
- Astro
- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- Redux
- Zustand
- Typescript
- Sanity
- Git
- MUI
- ANT Design
- Tailwind

FAMILIAR

- Vue
- Ionic
- Gatsby
- AndroidNodeis
- Express
- Mongo
- iOS

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

CERTIFICATIONS

- <u>Frontend Developer(React)</u>
 <u>HackerRank</u>
 ce6fe36bde1b
- Problem Solving (Intermediate) — HackerRank — f72e358e348d

JavaScript (Intermediate)

— **HackerRank** - 2243cc909875

• Namaste React Live Course

— NamasteDev— QTMWG2ET

EDUCATION

Birla Vishvakarma Mahavidyalaya (BVM), Anand — (B.E.) Computer Engineering — July 2013 - December 2020.